pdfbuddy.com 2015-06-05

# Privacy Policy | PDF Buddy

PDF Buddy respects your privacy. This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the Website. This policy describes our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.

This policy applies to information we collect through this Website. It does not apply to information collected by us through any other means, including through other websites operated by any third party, or through any application or content that may link to the Website.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding how we treat your information. By using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

#### Information We Collect

When accessing our Website, PDF Buddy will learn certain information about you during your visit. How we will handle information we learn about you depends upon what you do when visiting our site. For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, PDF Buddy uses software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.

If you visit our Website to read or download information on our pages, we may collect and store the following information about you: 

  * The name of the domain from which you access the Internet;
  * The IP address from which you access our Website;
  * The type of browser and operating system used to access our Website;
  * The date and time you access our site; and
  * The Internet address of the website you used to link directly to our site.

PDF Buddy will not obtain personally-identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us, nor will such information be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without the approval of the user at the time of collection.

If you identify yourself by sending us an e-mail containing personal information, then the information collected will be solely used to respond to your message.

If you upload Content to our Website, we may store and manipulate that content.

#### How We Store Your Content and Collected Information

  * All Content/Information is stored in the U.S., in data centers operated by Amazon Web Services.
  * Only PDF Buddy administrators and the administrators of the underlying service platforms will have access to stored Content/Information.
  * Uploaded files will be stored until you delete them or close your account.
  * Uploaded files not associated with an account will be automatically deleted after several days.
  * Basic account information like email and IP addresses may be retained after an account is closed to prevent duplicate sign ups as per our Terms of Service.

#### How We Use Collected Information

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information: 

  * To present our Website and its contents to you;
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us;
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it;
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection; and
  * To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide through it.

Some information collected is for statistical purposes. PDF Buddy may use software programs to create summary statistics, which are used for such purposes as assessing the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, what information is of most and least interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas. PDF Buddy uses Google Analytics to anonymously track site metrics.

#### Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose aggregated information about our users without restriction. We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provided as described in this privacy policy: 

  * To our subsidiaries, affiliates, and clients;
  * To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business;
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provided it; and
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.

We may also disclose your personal information: 

  * To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request;
  * To enforce or apply our Terms of Service (<https://www.pdfbuddy.com/terms>) and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes; and
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of PDF Buddy, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

#### Accessing and Correcting Your Information

You can make updates to your contact information on the Website. You may also send us an e-mail at support@pdfbuddy.com to correct any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

#### Children Under the Age of 13

Our Website is not for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any information to the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not: 

  * use or provide any information on this Website;
  * make any purchases through the Website;
  * provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may use.

If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at support@pdfbuddy.com.

#### Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to support@pdfbuddy.com.

#### Data Security

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

#### Contact Information

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at:  
PDF Buddy  
34 Berry St. Apt 3M  
Brooklyn, NY 11249  
Email: support@pdfbuddy.com
